https://www.whoopassenterprises.com/privacy-policy/

BLOG
You are here:
Effective Date: June 13, 2007
Whoopass Enterprises, LLC values the users of our website (the "Website"). Your privacy and trust are very important to us. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we collect when you use the Website and the services offered on the Website ("Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services"). This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@whoopassenterprises.com
Does Whoopass Enterprises, LLC Ever Make Changes to its Privacy Policy?
We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by sending you an email, posting a notice on the home page of the Website, or posting a notice in your account when you first login after we have made changes. If you receive notification of a change in our Privacy Policy, you must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures. You may not be able to receive notices from us if your cookies are not set to accept and/or are disabled.
What Types of Information Does Whoopass Enterprises, LLC Collect From Me?
Personal Information. We collect Personal Information that you provide to us, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number, and financial information. We will also collect photos related to the product order that you are placing, and potentially logos, other images and a description of your order.
Non-Personal Information. We also collect non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address ("Non-Personal Information"). Non-Personal Information cannot be easily used to personally identify you.
How and When Does Whoopass Enterprises, LLC Collect This Information?
Providing Information to Us. We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you purchase a product sold through a Shop, we may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, and email address. If you create a Shopkeeper or Affiliate Account, we may collect your name, tax identification number, mailing address, email address, and other information that we request during the registration process, and any information that you provide to Whoopass Enterprises affiliates. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, we will collect your email address.
Communications With Us. If you communicate with us regarding the Website or the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and/or services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.
Analytic and Reporting Technologies. Like the operators of most websites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software, operating system types, clickstream patterns, and the dates and times that the Website and the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services are accessed. We also contract with several online partners to help manage, monitor and optimize our Website and the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services and to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications and how visitors use the Website. To do this, we may use web beacons and cookies.
How Does Whoopass Enterprises, LLC Use My Information?
Personal Information. We use Personal Information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products, services, and the Website, fulfilling requests for information, producing and shipping the products that you order, and providing customer support. For example, if you sign up to receive a Whoopass Enterprises newsletter, we will use the email address you provide to send you the newsletters.
We will not use your photos, written communications or any other information from your order on our website or in other marketing materials, without your permission, generally given through an email approval. Such permission may be revoked and we will remove the previously approved content from our website within 10 working days. However, any pre-printed materials including the content will continue to be used until the existing supply is exhausted.
Non-Personal Information. We use Non-Personal Information to track the use of the Website and Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and servcies and for other internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Whoopass Enterprises products and services and the Website.
When Will Whoopass Enterprises, LLC Disclose My Information to Third Parties?
Disclosure to Successors. We may disclose your Personal Information to any successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that acquires us. In the event Whoopass Enterprises, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by or with another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or by a notice on our Website of any such change in ownership or control of your Personal Information.
Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third Parties. We may disclose your Personal Information to prevent an emergency, to prevent harm to others, to respond to legal requirements, to protect or enforce our rights and policies, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order).
Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers and Online Partners. We may contract with various third parties who help us provide, maintain and improve the Website and the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services. For example, we use a third party to process payments made to us, and may subcontract production, fulfillment, analytics, reporting or other operations. We also contract with several online partners to help manage, monitor and optimize our Website and the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services and to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications and how visitors use the Website. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your Personal Information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. We cannot guarantee that such third parties will not disclose your Personal Information.
Disclosure of Non-Personal Information. We will disclose Non-Personal Information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, investors, customers, and others. You may not opt-out of the sharing of this information. However, it cannot be easily used to identify you personally.
What About Cookies and Web Beacons?
A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies. We use cookies to track your use of the Website and the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services, to provide you with a more personalized user experience, and to allow you to login and begin use of the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services automatically when you visit the Website.
A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than a 1x1 pixel that is placed on a web page or in an e-mail that is used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the Website or receiving the e-mail.
Cookies and web beacons used by Whoopass Enterprises, LLC and our online partners are not linked to Personal Information. Some of our Shopkeepers may use cookies or web beacons on our Website. We have no access to or control over these cookies and web beacons. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies and web beacons by Whoopass Enterprises, LLC and our online partners only and does not cover the use of cookies or web beacons by any other third party, Shopkeeper or advertiser.
Does Whoopass Enterprises, LLC Protect My Personal Information?
Personal Information. Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.
How Can I Review and Make Changes to My Personal Information?
You can obtain a copy of and request that we correct errors in your Personal Information by emailing us at info@whoopassenterpries.com. For your protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity to obtain a copy of your Personal Information. If your Personal Information changes or if you no longer want to use the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services, you may correct, update or deactivate your Personal Information and/or your account through the account management screen. If you would like to deactivate or terminate your account you can also contact us at info@whoopassenterprises.com.
Tell-A-Friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about the Website or the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Website. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number and/or social security number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Does This Privacy Policy Apply When I Access Third Party Websites?
You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider.
What About Children's Privacy?
Under Thirteen. The Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services are intended for users ages 13 and older only. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13.
Thirteen to Seventeen. Prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 can only use the Whoopass Enterprises, LLC products and services under their parents or legal guardian's supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we deactivate any of your Personal Information in our database and/or opt-out from receiving communications from us. If you wish to do so, please contact us at info@whoopassenterprises.com.
Can I Opt-Out From Receiving Communications From Whoopass Enterprises, LLC?
We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used for certain purposes. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at info@whoopassenterprises.com. We also offer you an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications through the account management screen. If you need assistance you may contact us at info@whoopassenterprises.com.
If we disclose your Personal Information to a third party in a manner that is not set forth in this Privacy Policy you will be notified so that you can make an informed choice about sharing your Personal Information with that third party.
How can extra, returned and unused bobbleheads be used?
Whoopass Enterprises may use any extra copies, returned or unused custom bobbleheads or others products as samples for potential customers. These products will not be made for sale.
How are images of my doll used?
Whoopass Enterprises reserves the right to send images of the custom bobblehead dolls or other products to the email address provided by the customer at the time of ordering. These images may be superimposed on various background scenes, included in video games or included in video productions. Any forwarding or sending of these images to others beyond the party ordering the product - whether authorized or unauthorized, in electronic or physical form is not the responsibility of Whoopass Enterprises.
Whoopass Enterprises will ask for permission from you before using your doll in any public forum, including on our website or in promotional offerings.
Custom Body
Head-to-toe customCustom 2-on-1 baseCustom WeddingCar Bobble HeadPet Bobble HeadMusician Bobble Head
Stock Body
Wedding & GraduationSports bobble headWork & CasualVehiclesKids bobble headZombie bobbleheadsPet bobbles
View all Bobblehead Categories
Other custom products
Sculpted OrnamentsPainted OrnamentsPoker Card CoversGolf Club CoversLarge Pet PaintingsSmall Pet PaintingsHousewaresCustom Poker Chips
View all Custom Products
% done
Get a free custom mockup within 2 hours!
Yes, get it for free
No, thanks
How can we reach you to ask details for mockup?
Email:
Phone Number:
Next»
Upload your picture:
Describe your Bubblehead:
Get mockup for free
Thank you!
Your request was sent to our manager
Create another mockup
